# **Drew Perkins**

1011 Stonegate Road | Greenwood, IN | (317) 296-4015 drew.m.perkins@gmail.com

# **Summary**

I'm passionate about bringing visions into reality. Having served in the armed forces, I'm not afraid of a challenge, but instead welcome the opportunity to keep improving. The fine details, code quality, and superior customer satisfaction are important goals I always set out to achieve. I'm happiest when I can apply critical thinking to solving complex problems or simply making things better. Currently solving engineering\manufacturing problems at Knauf Insulation.

#### **Skills**

VMware ESXi | Windows Server | .NET Core - C# | Angular | Docker | Nginx | Git | GoLang | Typescript | T-SQL | REST | Entity Framework\Dapper ORMs

# **Employment History**

**Knauf Insulation**SENIOR DEVELOPER
Shelbyville, Indiana
August 2019 – Present

- Managed Windows 2019 servers to ensure website and data reliability.
- DevOps server management with Docker containers and alerting system to verify all core websites\services were active. (Docker, Nginx, IIS, SQL)
- Worked directly with managers\plant staff across multiple departments to improve their daily job duties by providing automated software solutions, reports, or live charts.
- Fully responsive QA website to dynamically generate form with spec validation based on chosen product, and automatically calculate test data values for the quality operators. (.NET Core, Angular, MSSQL)
- National website for all plants to access data \ reports \ charts. (.NET Core, Angular, MSSQL)

## **Indiana Southern District Court**

DEVELOPER\IT SUPPORT Indianapolis, Indiana September 2016 – August 2019

- Monitored SolarWinds Network Performance Monitor (NPM) to monitor switch performance. Switch security and minimal downtime were critical for the federal staff employees.
- Managed Quest KACE patch management to ensure all computers remained up to date on critical security patches, and reduced electrical usage by \$10,000/year by implementing proper sleep schedules.
- Attended VMWare Horizon\ESXi training to assist in maintaining virtual environment.
- Utilized Microsoft Deployment Toolkit (MDT) to build\maintain Windows 10 images.
- Assisted in management of RHEL servers to ensure database was secure\performant.
- Developed stand-alone Windows application (C#, Entity Framework, Informix SQL & MySQL) for IT teams to manage users/computers across multiple federal circuit courts.
- Office 365 macro development (VB.NET) to interact with IBM Informix SQL database and build court documents dynamically.
- Created website (ASP.NET MVC, C#, Entity Framework, IBM Informix) with login pass-through and a focus on case management.
- Developed Acrobat template documents utilizing SOAP and JavaScript to increase document processing productivity.
- Developed Acrobat plug-in (C#, REST, C++) to increase document processing productivity.

#### Circle K Corp

### JUNIOR SYSTEMS ADMINISTRATOR

September 2014 – September 2016

- Managed domain controllers, print servers, Symantec Endpoint Protection Manager (SEPM) server, switches, and PBX system.
- Assigned as the Tier 3 level of support ensuring timely completion of work orders by working alongside engineering/development teams. Improved security posture by utilizing AppLocker to reduce ransomware infections. IE, Adobe Flash, Java, and Silverlight kept updated to prevent Axpergle exploits.
- Developed applications to assist IT store support staff to understand quickly each store networks intricacies and possible down equipment.
- Assigned to programmatically deploy new software applications to corporate machines by developing C# and PowerShell scripts and utilizing BITS technology.
- Automated multiple Tier 2 tasks to increase productivity and ensure high data validation.
- Assisted in migrating 600 corporate machines from Windows 7 to Windows 8.1 utilizing USMT and SCCM 2012.
- Saved company \$4,000 developing phone management application utilizing C# and Java programming languages.
- Assembled/Deployed 8 multifunction printers, created their associated printer share on the print server, and developed an ASP.NET C# web application for the management of the printer fleet using SNMPv2.

#### U.S. Army

#### **DESKTOP SUPPORT SPECIALIST**

July 2008 – June 2015

- Upgraded Windows servers quarterly to comply with IAVA. Designed/Engineered enterprise domain with 6 Windows Server 2008 R2 machines, with attention to redundancy in case of hardware/power failure, by utilizing RAID backup solution and UPS. Server features installed/configured included WDS, WSUS, DHCP, DNS, and Exchange 2007.
- Installed\Managed Cisco routers and switches to build entire network infrastures from start to finish in a high stress environment where uptime is of the upmost importance.
- Diagnosed and troubleshooted UNIX and Windows processing problems and applied solutions to increase efficiency. Trained junior members of IT team regarding network security and troubleshooting of data circuits.

## **Education**

Alumnus of IUPUI, Indianapolis, IN

Certifications: CCNA | CompTIA A+ | CompTIA Security+